Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2014
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: clarinetist Adrián Sandí, flutist Kelli Kathman, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, violist Isabel Hagen, and doublebassist Greg Chudzik at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: rehearsal Requiscat (2010).tif (Image-file jib2014_147)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: doublebassist Greg Chudzik, violist Isabel Hagen, violinists Will Knuth and Yuki Numata Resnick, and pianist Oliver Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7203rehearsal JIB.tif (Image-file jib2014_148)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: flutist Kelli Kathman and violist Isabel Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7209Sungmin Shin quitar David Felder Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_149)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: pianist Oliver Hagen, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violist Isabel Hagen, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, and doublebassist Greg Chudzik at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_721 rehearsal David Felder Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_150)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, and violist Isabel Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7214reheasal Ensembal Signal David Felder Requiscat ( 2010).tif (Image-file jib2014_151)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and composer David Felder in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014 with bass player Greg Chudzik in the background, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Brad Lubman conductor David Felder Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_152)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and composer David Felder in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7218Brad Lubman conductor David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_153)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and composer David Felder in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7219David Fellder Brad Lubman.tif (Image-file jib2014_154)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and guitarist Sungmin Shin performing with members of Ensemble Signal: pianist Oliver Hagen, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, violist Isabel Hagen, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, and double bassist Greg Chudzik at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7234David Felder Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_155)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with composer David Felder onstage after a performance of Felder's Requiescat with members of Ensemble Signal: violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7235David Felder Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_156)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with composer David Felder onstage after a performance of Felder's Requiescat with guitarist Sungmin Shin and members of Ensemble Signal: pianist Oliver Hagen, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Brad Lubman conductor Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_157)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with composer David Felder onstage after a performance of Felder's Requiescat with guitarist Sungmin Shin and members of Ensemble Signal: pianist Oliver Hagen, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, percussionist Bill Solomon, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder Requiescat (2010) Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_158)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and oboist Jacqueline Leclair performing with members of Ensemble Signal: violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7239Ensemble Signal Rands CONCERTINO (1996).tif (Image-file jib2014_159)
- Oboist Jacqueline Leclair and composer Bernard Rands onstage with harpist Sophie Rusnock and violinist Yuki Numata Resnick after a performance of Rands's Concertino at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7240Bernard Rands Jacqueline Leclair oboe CONCERTINO(1996).tif (Image-file jib2014_160)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, oboist Jacqueline Leclair and composer Bernard Rands onstage with members of Ensemble Signal: harpist Sophie Rusnock, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky after a performance of Rands's Concertino at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7241Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_161)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, oboist Jacqueline Leclair and composer Bernard Rands onstage with members of Ensemble Signal: harpist Sophie Rusnock, violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman (obscured), clarinetist Adrián Sandí (obscured), violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky after a performance of Rands's Concertino at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7242Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_162)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and pianist Oliver Hagen performing Philippe Hurel's Interstices with Ensemble Signal percussionists Carson Moody, Bill Solomon, and Nick Tolle at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7243Philippe Hurel.tif (Image-file jib2014_163)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and pianist Oliver Hagen performing Philippe Hurel's Interstices with Ensemble Signal percussionists Carson Moody, Bill Solomon, and Nick Tolle at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7246Philippe Hurel Interstices.tif (Image-file jib2014_164)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti performing with Ensemble Signal: cimbalom player Nick Tolle, violist Isabel Hagen, percussionist Bill Solomon, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, horn player Kate Sheeran, percussionist Caron Moody, and double bassist Greg Chudzik at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7248Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_165)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti performing with Ensemble Signal members, violist Isabel Hagen, flutist Kelli Kathman, and percussionist Bill Solomon at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7250 Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_166)
- Conductor Brad Lubman shaking hands with violinist Irvine Arditti with Ensemble Signal members, percussionist Bill Solomon and violist Isabel Hagen (obscured) after a performance of Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7251Iving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_167)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti onstage with members of Ensemble Signal, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, flutist Kelli Kathman, and violist Isabel Hagen after a performance Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7254Irvine Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_168)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti onstage with Ensemble Signal members, cimbalom player Nick Tolle, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, flutist Kelli Kathman, violist Isabel Hagen, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, horn player Kate Sheeran, and double bassist Greg Chudzik after a performance of Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7255Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_169)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti onstage with Ensemble Signal members, cimbalom player Nick Tolle, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, flutist Kelli Kathman, violist Isabel Hagen, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, horn player Kate Sheeran, and double bassist Greg Chudzik after a performance of Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7256Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_170)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, composer Hilda Paredes, and violinist Irvine Arditti with Ensemble Signal: cimbalom player Nick Tolle, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, flutist Kelli Kathman, and violist Isabel Hagen after a performance of Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7257Hilda Paredes.tif (Image-file jib2014_171)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, composer Hilda Paredes, and violinist Irvine Arditti with Ensemble Signal members, cimbalom player Nick Tolle, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, flutist Kelli Kathman, and clarinetist Adrián Sandí after a performance of Hilda Paredes's Senales at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7258composer Hilda Paredes Irving Arditti Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_172)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta and composer Bernard Rands with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7265Buffalo Philharmonic Rehearsal Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_173)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta and composer Stephen Hartke with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7273 BPO.tif (Image-file jib2014_174)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta rehearsing the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7274Buffalo Philharmonic.tif (Image-file jib2014_175)
- Composer Stephen Hartke examining score at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7282Stephen Hartke.tif (Image-file jib2014_176)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta rehearsing the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7287BPO.tif (Image-file jib2014_177)
- Conductor Brad Lubman in rehearsal with pianist Oliver Hagen, and Ensemble Signal members percussionist Nick Tolle, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, and violist Isabel Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Untitled-1Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_178)
- Conductor Julien Leroy rehearsing Ensemble Court-Circuit members, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: =Ensemble Court Circuit (Image-file jib2014_179)
- Conductor Julien Leroy rehearsing Ensemble Court-Circuit members, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and pianist Jean-Marie Cottet at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_180)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.